<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<Defs>
	<!--If you are translating these rules, please do not touch any keywords(enclosed by [] or {}). -->
	<!--To make this mod works in your language, you need to translate text after an arrow("->") symbol. -->
	<!--Be aware, they are very vulnerable for typos and case sensitive issues.-->
	<RulePackDef>
		<defName>RotR_Rule_Quests</defName>
		<rulePack>
			<rulesStrings>
				<!-- ==================Entry==================== -->
				<li>title_bondoffreedom->Bond of Freedom</li>
				<li>desc_bondoffreedom->{slave_nameFull} and {lover_nameFull} are in love. Driven by a profound sense of compassion, {lover_nameDef} is determined to liberate {lover_possessive} beloved from the shackles of slavery. \n\nUpon the successful emancipation, {slave_nameDef} will join the colony as colonist.\n\nHowever, this act of mercy may stir discontent among your fellow colonists, challenging the harmony within your ranks. Choose wisely.</li>
				<li>title_orphanlover->Orphan Lover</li>
				<li>desc_orphanlover->Two young wanderers, {boy_nameFull} and {girl_nameFull} have arrived at our colony's gates.\n\nBound not by blood but by a shared history of loss and survival, they have journeyed through perilous landscapes, evading threats both human and natural in search of a sanctuary.\n\nWill we extend our compassion and resources to help them or prioritize our colony's safety and stability by turning them away?</li>
				<li>title_crush->Crush</li>
				<li>desc_crush->Amidst the unending cycle of survival and solidarity in the colony, an unexpected tenderness has begun to unfold between two of its members.\n\n{initiator_nameFull} finds {initiator_objective}self caught in the grip of newfound affection towards {other_nameFull}.\n\nThis burgeoning affection, delicate and unspoken, is shadowed by uncertainty, a lingering question of whether the feelings are mirrored in {other_possessive} heart.\n\nCaught in the dance between desire and doubt, {initiator_nameDef} is teetering between reaching out or retreat.</li>
				<li>title_secretadmirer->Secret Admirer</li>
				<li>desc_secretadmirer->In the day-to-day life of the colony, {initiator_nameFull} has begun to suspect that {other_nameFull} might harbor secret feelings for {initiator_objective}.\n\nThis suspicion arises from a series of nuanced interactions and perhaps unintentional hints that {other_nameDef} has dropped, stirring a mixture of emotions in {initiator_nameDef}, from flattered curiosity to a cautious hesitation.\n\n{initiator_pronoun} is at a crossroads of interpreting {other_nameDef}'s behavior and deciding how to respond.</li>
				<li>title_kidneytrade->Kidney Trade</li>
				<li>desc_kidneytrade->{trader_nameFull} arrived at your colony. {trader_pronoun} might have something to trade.</li>
				<li>title_adoptchance->Adoption Chance</li>
				<li>desc_adoptchance->The baby, {child_nameFull}, once saved and nurtured in good care, has grown under the watchful eyes and kind hearts of {child_possessive} guardians.\n\nNow, at {child_possessive} birthday, this young soul has expressed a profound desire to formalize the bond,  wishing for {father_nameDef} and {mother_nameDef} to become {child_possessive} official parents.\n\nHow will you respond to this heartfelt plea?</li>
			</rulesStrings>
		</rulePack>
	</RulePackDef>

</Defs>